db.questions.insertMany([
  {
    question: "How many holes are there in a full round of golf?",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["21", "24", "30", "18"],
    answer: "18"
  },
  {
    question: "How many soccer players should be on the field at the same time?",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Number Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "22"
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: In Tennis, the first to score after deuce has a disadvantage.",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "True or False",
    choices: ["True","False"],
    answer: "false"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the 'perfect score' in a single game of Ten Pin Bowling?",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["100","200","300","400"],
    answer: "300"
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: Tennis 6-0 is a sport where you find a Bagel.",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "True or False",
    choices: ["True","False"],
    answer: "true"
  },
  {
  question: "How many balls are used in a game of Pool?",
  difficulty: "Medium",
  category: "Sports",
  type: "Multiple Choice",
  choices: ["15","16","17","18"],
  answer: "16"
  },
  {
    question: "In which Olympic swimming races do competitors start in the water? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "backstroke"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the English football player that has a daughter named Harper Seven?",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "david beckham"
  },
  {
    question: "Which nation’s football team won the 1970 FIFA World Cup? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Brazil","Argentina", "Germany", "Thailand"],
    answer: "brazil"
  },
  {
    question: "True or False: Joseph S. Blatter became president of fifa in June 1998? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "True or False",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "true"
  },
  {
    question: "How many feet high is the top of badminton net above the court?",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Number Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "5"
  },                                                                                 
  {
    question: "Which boxing weight category had a maximum weight limit of 9 stone? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "featherweight"
  },
  {
    question: "George Muresan and Manute Bol are the tallest players in NBA history. How tall are they?  ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["7’7’’/2.31m","6’7’’/2.01m","6’5’’/1.96m","7’5’’/2.26m"],
    answer: "7’7’’/2.31m"
  },
  {
    question: "What did Goran Ivanisevic refrain from doing at Wimbledon in 1994, to win a $2,000 bet? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Eating Cake","Throwing his racket","Cursing", "Winning the game"],
    answer: "throwing his racket"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first Russian tennis player to win a Grand Slam singles title, in 1996? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Sports",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "yevgeny kefelnikov"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the smallest planet in our solar system?",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Mercury","Venus","Earth","Mars"],
    answer: "mercury"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the largest planet in our solar system?",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Jupiter","The Sun", "Saturn", "Pluto"],
    answer: "Jupiter"
  },
  {
    question: "What planet is known as the red planet? ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Mars", "Uranus", "Urethra", "Venus"],
    answer: "mars"
  },
  {
    question: "Earth is located in which galaxy?",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "milky way galaxy"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the 2nd biggest planet in our solar system?",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Saturn", "Mars", "Jupiter", "Venus"],
    answer: "saturn"
  },
  {
    question: "Is the sun a star or a planet? ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["A Star", "A planet"],
    answer: "a star"
  },
   {
    question: "True or False: The Hubble Space Telescope is the name of NASA’s most famous space telescope.",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "True or False",
    choices: ["True", "False"],
    answer: "true"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the first satellite sent into space? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "sputnik"
  },
  {
    question: "Ganymede is a moon of which planet? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "",
    choices: ["Jupiter", "The Sun", "Neptune","Pluto"],
    answer: "jupiter"
  },
  {
    question: "Who invented the telescope? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "hans lippershey"
  },
  {
    question: "WHen did the space age begin",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["1957","1956","1958","1959"],
    answer: "1957"
  },
  {
    question: "Approximately how many trillion miles are there in a light year? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["6.9","5.9","6.1","7.1"],
    answer: "5.9"
  },
  {
    question: "The day on which the Sun’s direct rays cross the celestial equator is called",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "the equinox"
  },
  {
    question: "What term describes the alignment of three celestial bodies? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "syzygy"
  },
  {
    question: "How many minutes does it take for light from the sun to reach earth? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["100","6","7","8"],
    answer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: "Which year was the first exoplanet discovered in? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Astronomy and Space",
    type: "Number Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "1995"
  },
  {
    question: "Finish the lyric: \"It's hard to believe that I couldn't ___\" (High School Musical)",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["breathe", "see", "smell", "taste"],
    answer: "see"
  },
  {
    question: "Finish the lyric: \"___ me baby one more time\" (Britney Spears)",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Carry", "Love", "Push", "Hit"],
    answer: "hit"
  },
  {
    question: "Finish the lyric: \"Look what you made me ___\" (Taylor Swift)",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["blew", "spew", "do", "what I'm meant to be"],
    answer: "do"
  },
  {
    question: "Finish the lyric: \"Well they say people come, they say people _____\" (Coldplay)",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["know", "grow", "go", "dough"],
    answer: "go"
  },
  {
    question: "Finish the lyric: \"I tried so hard and ___\" (Linkin Park)",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["caviar", "saw my worth", "succeeded", "got so far"],
    answer: "got so far"
  },
  {
    question: "Finish the lyric: \"I will be rising from the ground like a ___\" (Demi Lovato)",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["sledgehammer", "sly hamster", "watchtower", "skyscraper"],
    answer: "skyscraper"
  },
  {
    question: "What year was the song \"Firework\" by Katy Perry released?",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Number Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "2010"
  },
  {
    question: "What year was the song \"Complicated\" by Avril Lavigne released?",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Number Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "2002"
  },
  {
    question: "What year was the song \"Yellow\" by Coldplay released? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Number Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "2000"
  },
  {
    question: "What year was the song \"Umbrella\" by Rihanna released?  ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Number Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "2007"
  },
  {
    question: "What year was the song \"Lovebug\" by the Jonas Brothers released?  ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Number Answer",
    choices: [],
    answer: "2008"
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the Album of the Year award during the 53rd Annual Grammy's?",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Justin Bieber", "Taylor Swift", "Coldplay", "Arcade Fire"],
    answer: "arcade fire"
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the Record of the Year award during the 54th Annual Grammy's?",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Adele", "Beyonce", "Bruno Mars", "Bon Iver"],
    answer: "adele"
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the Record of the Year award during the 55th Annual Grammy's?",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Frank Ocean", "Gotye", "Mumford & Sons", "Fun"],
    answer: "gotye"
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the Best Rock Song award during the 57th Annual Grammy's?",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Muse", "The Black Keys", "Jack White", "Paramore"],
    answer: "paramore"
  },
  {
    question: "Who won the Best Pop Vocal Album award during the 56th Annual Grammy's? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Music",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Bruno Mars",  "Lana del Rey", "Lorde", "Katy Perry"] ,
    answer: "bruno mars"
  },
  //animals
  {
    question: "Which brain is the cat’s brain most similar to? ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Dog's","Human's","Cow's","Monkey's"] ,
    answer: "Human's"
  },
  {
    question: "T or F. A cat, standing in a still position, can jump up to 6 times its own length? ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "True or False",
    choices: ["True","False"] ,
    answer: "True"
  },
  {
    question: "What do you call a group of fish? ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["herd", "frenzy", "school", "swarm"] ,
    answer: "school"
  },
  {
    question: "T or F the humps seen on camels are used for water storage? ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "True or False",
    choices: ["True", "False"] ,
    answer: "False"
  },
  {
    question: "The daily diet of a panda consists almost entirely of what plant? ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Rosemary", "Bay Leaf", "Bamboo", "Tulipwood"] ,
    answer: "Bamboo"
  },
  {
    question: "A cat has how many whiskers, on average? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["20","21","22","24"] ,
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "Do cats have fewer teeth than dogs have, or more? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["More", "Less", "Same"] ,
    answer: "Less"
  },
    {
    question: "Outdoor-only cats live, on average, about how many years? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["3-5", "7-10", "12-15", "9-12"] ,
    answer: "3-5"
  },
  {
    question: "A term for a group of cats is? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Clowder", "clutch", "caggle", "covey"] ,
    answer: "Clowder"
  },
   {
    question: "Where were hamsters discovered? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [] ,
    answer: "Syria"
  },
   {
    question: "What do you call a group of eagles? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["scoop", "squadron", "convocation", "bevy"] ,
    answer: "convocation"
  },
   {
    question: "Drawings of this huge dog were on Egyptian monuments 5,000 years ago ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["MASTIFF", "Great Pyreness", "Greate Dane", "Saint bernard"] ,
    answer: "MASTIFF"
  },
  {
    question: "Which dog has a holy history? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Pekingese", "Lhasa apso", "Tibetan Spaniel", "Schiepperke"] ,
    answer: "Lhasa apso"
  },
   {
    question: "This is the national dog of France. ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Bichon Frise", "French Bulldog", "Poodle", "Brittany"] ,
    answer: "Poodle"
  },
  {
    question: "A term for a group of kittens is:  ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [] ,
    answer: "Kindle"
  },
   {
    question: "All of the following are the names of cat breeds, except:  ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Animals",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Balinese", "Beauceron", "burmilla", "birman"] ,
    answer: "Beauceron"
  },
   {
    question: "What is another name for Superman?  ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["The Red Redeemer" ,"The Masked Avenger" ,"The Caped Crusader", "The man of steel"] ,
    answer: "The man of steel"
  },
   {
    question: "What is Superman's only weakness?  ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [] ,
    answer: "Kryptonite"
   },
   {
    question: "What is the name of Batman's alter ego?  ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Bruce Devon", "Bruce Wayne", "Bruce Davis", "Devon Bruce"] ,
    answer: "Bruce Wayne"
   },
   {
    question: "Batman protects what place?  ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["New York City", "Hell's Kitchen", "Gotham City", "San Francisco"] ,
    answer: "Gotham City"
   },
   {
    question: "How did Spiderman get his superpowers?  ",
    difficulty: "Easy",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["He was experimented on in a lab", "He trained hard to get his powers", "Bitten by radioactive spider", "He was born with it"] ,
    answer: "Bitten by radioactive spider"
   },
    {
    question: "All have been nicknames of batman except?  ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["World's Greatest Vigilante", "The Dark Knight", "The Caped Crusader", "World's Greatest Detective"] ,
    answer: "World's Greatest Vigilante"
   },
   {
    question: "This superhero's supertools included bullet-proof bracelets and a magic lasso:  ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Wonder Woman", "Super Girl", "Catwoman", "Elastigirl"] ,
    answer: "Wonder Woman"
   },
   {
    question: "The Green Lantern has also used this name as a secret identity:  ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Barry Allen", "Kyle Rayner", "John Dickering", "Britt Reid"] ,
    answer: "Kyle Rayner"
   },
   {
    question: "The Sandman appears in which superhero movie? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Blade", "Spiderman3", "The Incredible Hulk", "X-men 2"] ,
    answer: "Spiderman3"
   },
   {
    question: "What's the alter ego of Wonder Woman? ",
    difficulty: "Medium",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Selina Kyle", "Ororo Munroe", "Susan Storm" ,"Diana Prince"] ,
    answer: "Diana Prince"
   },
   {
    question: "In the movie Anchorman, Ron Burgundy says that what superhero was denied a bank loan? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["The Phantom", "The Flash", "The Punisher", "The Human Torch"] ,
    answer: "The Human Torch"
   },
    {
    question: "The Kingpin appears in which superhero movie? ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [] ,
    answer: "Daredevil"
   },
   {
    question: "T or F. Is Dr. Victor Fries the alter ego of Mr. Freeze?  ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "True or False",
    choices: ["True","False"] ,
    answer: "True"
   },
   {
    question:  "Who is the love interest of The Rocketeer?  ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Text Answer",
    choices: [] ,
    answer: "Jenny Blake"
   },
   {
    question:  "Marvel Comics owned the rights to this word from 1975 through 1996, when they realized it was impossible to enforce the trademark:  ",
    difficulty: "Hard",
    category: "Superheroes",
    type: "Multiple Choice",
    choices: ["Zombie", "Hero", "Mutant", "Monster"] ,
    answer: "Zombie"
   }
]);